<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>研究 on 中條研究室</title><link>/studies/</link><description>Recent content in 研究 on 中條研究室</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ja-jp</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/studies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2023年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2023/</guid><description>論文誌 Keita Fukada, Kataru Hara, Jingyong Cai, Daichi Teruya, Ikuko Shimizu, Takatsugu Kuriyama, Katsumi Koga, Kosuke Sakamoto, Yoshiyuki Nakamura, Hironori Nakajo “An Automatic Tomato Growth Analysis System Using YOLO Transfer Learning” Appl. Sci. 2023, 13(12), 6880.　https://doi.org/10.3390/app13126880 国際会議 Kentaro Machida, Tetsuya Nakamura, Jingyong Cai, Thinh Nguyen-Quang, Duc Anh Pham, Han Huy-Dung, Huy Hoang Nguyen, Taiichiro Ookawa, Hironori Nakajo, “Navigable Areas Segmentation Method for Unmanned Surface Vehicles in Paddy Fields”, IEEE R10 Humanitarian Technology Conference (HTC 2023), October 15-18, 2023, Rajkot, India, https://ieeexplore.</description></item><item><title>2022年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2022/</guid><description>国際会議 Hidetaro Tanaka, Tomoaki Tanaka, Ryosuke Higashi, Tsutomu Sekibe, Shuichi Takada, and Hironori Nakajo. 2022. Implementation of a RISC- V SMT Core in an AI processor. In The 11th International Symposium on Information and Communication Technology (SoICT 2022), December 1–3, 2022, Hanoi, Vietnam. ACM, 8 pages. （Best Poster Award 受賞） https://doi.org/10.1145/3568562.3568634
Tanaka Tomoaki, Higashi Ryosuke, Tanaka Hidetaro, Miyoshi Takefumi, Osana Yasunori, Tada Jubee, Tanaka Kiyofumi, and Nakajo Hironori. 2022. Shared Vector Register of RISC-V for the Future Hardware Acceleration, The Sixth Workshop on RISC-V for Computer Architecture Research (CARRV) co-located with ISCA 2022, June 19th 2022, New York City, New York, USA, https://carrv.</description></item><item><title>2021年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2021/</guid><description>論文誌 Jingyong Cai, Masashi Takemoto, Yuming Qiu, Hironori Nakajo &amp;ldquo;Trigonometric Inference Providing Learning in Deep Neural Networks&amp;rdquo; Appl. Sci. 2021, 11, 6704.https://doi.org/10.3390/app11156704 Quoc Nguyen, Tomoaki Shikina, Daichi Teruya, Seiji Hotta, Huy-Dung Han, Hironori Nakajo &amp;ldquo;Leveraging Expert Knowledge for Label Noise Mitigation in Machine Learning&amp;rdquo; Appl. Sci. 2021, 11, 11040.https://doi.org/10.3390/app112211040 研究会発表 前田依莉子 ，照屋大地，中條拓伯,“再構成可能仮想アクセラレータ (ReVA) の実現に向けたキャッシュコヒーレントな相互接続規格の検討”,信学技報, vol. 121, no. 344, RECONF2021-80, pp. 132-137.2022 年 1 月 24 日 (月)-1 月 25 日 (火) オンライン開催 (RECONF, VLD, CPSY,IPSJ-ARC, IPSJ-SLDM).</description></item><item><title>2020年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2020/</guid><description> 論文誌 Daichi Teruya, Hironori Nakajo： &amp;ldquo;A Ruby-Based Hardware/Software Co-Design Environment with Functional Reactive Programming: Mulvery&amp;rdquo;,IEICE Transactions on Information and Systems,Vol. E103.D, No.9, pp.1929-1938, 2020. 研究会発表 山下遼太, 照屋大地, 中條拓伯&amp;quot;Scalaベースハードウェア開発環境における自動アーキテクチャ探索の検討&amp;quot;,信学技報, vol.120, no.339, RECONF2020-81, pp.131-136, 2021.1.</description></item><item><title>2019年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2019/</guid><description>論文誌 矢内奎太朗、長名保範、中條拓伯：Java言語ベース高位合成ツールによる高性能計算の実機による検証,情報処理学会論文誌,Vol.60 No.8, pp.1360-1369 (2019.8) 国際会議 Kesevan Veloo, Hayate Kojima, Shogo Takata, Masashi Nakamura and Hironori Nakajo: &amp;ldquo;Interactive Cultivation System for the Future IoT-based Agriculture&amp;rdquo;,The Seventh International Symposium on Computing and Networking (CANDAR'19),pp. 298-304 (2019.11.27). Toan Tran Viet, Nishikawa Rin, Thanh Le Tien, Takemoto Masashi, Hoai Tran Van, Binh Huynh Thi Thanh and Nakajo Hironori:&amp;ldquo;Cow estrus detection with low-frequency accelerometer sensor by unsupervised learning&amp;rdquo;,The 10th Symposium on Information and Communication Technology (SoICT2019),pp.</description></item><item><title>2018年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2018/</guid><description>論文誌 Hironori Nakajo, Yusuke Katoh, Hironari Yoshiuchi, and Yoshio Murata:&amp;ldquo;Scalable Hardware Mechanism for Partitioned Circuits Operation&amp;rdquo;,ECTI Transactions on Computer and Information Technology (ECTI-CIT),vol. 12, no. 2, pp. 90-97, Dec. 2018. Yo Nishiyama, Yuko Sasaki, Yuki Hirai, Hironori Nakajo and Keiichi Kaneko:&amp;ldquo;Fault-Tolerant Routing Based on Routing Capabilities in a Hyper-Star Graph&amp;rdquo;,Journal of Information Science &amp;amp; Engineering, Vol.34 Issue 6, pp.1353-1366, 2018.12. 国際会議 Yusuke Katoh, Hironari Yoshiuchi and Hironori Nakajo:&amp;ldquo;Operation in Partitioned Circuits with Scalable Hardware Mechanism&amp;quot;The 15th International Joint Conference on Computer Science and Software Engineering (JCSSE2018),Nakhon Pathom, Thailand, Jul.</description></item><item><title>2017年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2017/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2017/</guid><description>論文誌 竹本正志，鈴木涼太，梅野克彦，矢代昌之，龍池哲也，Richard Stahl，Geert Vanmeerbeeck，三好健文，中條拓伯:&amp;ldquo;Lens Free Imager の画像キャプチャシステムの設計と実装&amp;rdquo;，情報処理学会論文誌「組込みシステム工学」特集号Vol.58, No.8, pp.1348-1358 (2017.8). 国際会議 Y. Ishikawa, K. Yanai, K. Koike, T. Miyoshi and H. Nakajo:&amp;ldquo;Hardware Acceleration with Multi-Threading of Java-Based High Level Synthesis Tool&amp;rdquo;,ACM Proceedings of the International Symposium on Highly Efficient Accelerators and Reconfigurable Technologies (HEART 2017) ACM Digital Library． Ryoko Uno, Ryota Suzuki and Hironori Nakajo:&amp;ldquo;Who Got Scolded by Computer Programs?:Contrasting Two Groups with and without Entrenchment of a Novel Construction&amp;rdquo;,Book of Abstracts:the 14th International Cognitive Linguistics Conference, pp.</description></item><item><title>2016年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2016/</guid><description>論文誌 松田和也，三好健文，船田悟史，中條拓伯:&amp;ldquo;回路分割機能付きJava 言語ベース高位合成ツールにおける回路検証機構&amp;rdquo;，情報処理学会論文誌「組込みシステム工学」特集号, Vol.57, No.8, pp.1680-1689 (2016.8). 渡邊実，佐野健太郎，高前田伸也，三好健文，中條拓伯：&amp;ldquo;FPGA ハードウエア・アクセラレーション向け日の丸高位合成ツール&amp;rdquo;，電子情報通信学会論文誌招待論文, Vol.J100-B, No.1, pp.1-10 (2017.1). 鈴木涼太，竹本正志，梅野克彦，矢代昌之，龍池哲也，Richard STAHL，Geert VANMEERBEECK，Veerle REUMERS，Andy LAMBRECHTS，Huys ROELAND，三好健文，中條拓伯：&amp;ldquo;高性能Lens Free Imagerのためのハードウェア・アクセラレーション&amp;rdquo;，電子情報通信学会論文誌 Vol.J100-D, No.3 pp.331-340 (2017.3). 照屋大地，宮崎大智，中條拓伯：&amp;ldquo;PyJer：高位合成ツールとSoCを用いたIoT 向けデバイスプロトタイピングのためのフレームワーク&amp;rdquo;，電子情報通信学会論文誌 Vol.J100-D, No.3 pp.287-297 学生論文特集秀逸論文 (2017.3). 国際会議 Masashi Takemoto, Ryota Suzuki, Katsuhiko Umeno, Masayuki Yashiro, Tetsuya Ryuchi, Kohta Ohshima, Naoya Kitagawa and Hironori Nakajo::&amp;ldquo;Design of real-time advanced lens free imager&amp;rdquo;,ACM SoICT &amp;lsquo;16 Proceedings of the Seventh Symposium on Information and Communication Technology, pp.</description></item><item><title>2015年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2015/</guid><description>論文誌 松田和也，三好健文，船田悟史，中條拓伯:&amp;ldquo;Java 言語ベース高位合成ツールを用いた回路分割方式の実装と評価&amp;rdquo;，情報処理学会論文誌，Vol.56，No.8，pp.1582-1592, (2015.8). 国際会議 R. Suzuki and H. Nakajo:&amp;ldquo;Implementation of a RISC Processor with a Complex Instruction Accelerator&amp;rdquo;,Proc. of The 2015 4th ICT International Student Project Conference (ICT-ISPC 2015)(2015.05). 査読付国内シンポジウム 竹本正志, 鈴木涼太, P. Techawattanagan, 梅野克彦, 矢代昌之, 龍池哲也, R. Stahl,G.Vanmeerbeeck, V. Reumers, A. Lambrechts, H. Roeland, 三好 健文, 中條拓伯:&amp;ldquo;Lens Free Imager の実用化のための設計と実装&amp;rdquo;,組込みシステムシンポジウム2015(ESS2015)論文集, pp.2-9 (2015.10). 山下貴大，五十嵐雄太，中條拓伯:&amp;ldquo;Fortran ベース高位合成ツールFortRock の開発&amp;rdquo;,組込みシステムシンポジウム2015(ESS2015)論文集, pp.5-12 (2015.10). 五十嵐雄太，老子裕輝，中條拓伯:&amp;ldquo;高位合成におけるループパイプライン化の検討&amp;rdquo;,組込みシステムシンポジウム2015(ESS2015)論文集,pp.</description></item><item><title>2014年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2014/</guid><description>論文誌 堤 智昭，大島 浩太，小泉 稔，中條 拓伯：&amp;ldquo;高精度時刻同期を分散処理制御に活用したタイムアウェア処理方式&amp;rdquo;，情報処理学会論文誌「学生・若手研究者論文」特集号 Vol.56, No.3, pp.879-891 (2015.03). 小池 恵介，三好 健文，五十嵐 雄太，船田 悟史，中條 拓伯：&amp;ldquo;Java言語ベース高位合成ツールによるアクセラレータ開発環境&amp;rdquo;，電子情報通信学会論文誌 D，Vol.J98-D，No.3，pp.373-383 (2015.03). 国際会議 Hironori Nakajo, Kazuya Matsuda, Takefumi Miyoshi, Masashi Takemoto and Satoshi Funada:&amp;ldquo;A verification method of a partitioned circuit with a high level synthesis tool based on java language.&amp;rdquo;,Proc. of International Conference on Advanced Computing and Applications (ACOMP2014) pp.1-9 (2014.11). Sasaki, Yuko, Yuki Hirai, Hironori Nakajo, and Keiichi Kaneko:&amp;ldquo;A Fault-tolerant Routing Algorithm based on Safety Levels in a Hyper-Star Graph,&amp;rdquo;,Proceedings of the 2014 International Conference on Parallel and Distributed Processing Techniques and Applications, Vol.</description></item><item><title>2013年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2013/</guid><description>論文誌 榎戸健二，三好健文，小池恵介，船田悟史，藤波香織，中條拓伯：&amp;ldquo;高位合成系JavaRock による Reconfigurable Androidにおけるハードウェア・アクセラレーション&amp;rdquo;，情報処理学会論文誌「組込みシステム工学」特集号 Vol.55, No.2, pp.1027-1036 (2014.02). 堀部 拓也，清水 郁子，中條 拓伯：&amp;ldquo;GPUによる2次元アンサンブル経験的モード分解の高速実行&amp;rdquo;，電子情報通信学会論文誌 D，Vol.J97-D，No.3，pp.357-368 (学生論文特集秀逸論文）(2014.03). 査読付き国内会議 小池恵介，三好健文，船田悟史，中條拓伯:&amp;ldquo;Java言語ベース高位合成ツール JavaRock-Thrash の開発&amp;rdquo;,組込みシステムシンポジウム(ESS2013) 論文集, pp.41-48 (2013.10)(奨励賞　受賞) 松田和也，三好健文，船田悟史，中條拓伯: &amp;ldquo;高位合成ツールJavaRockの回路分割システム&amp;rdquo;,組込みシステムシンポジウム(ESS2013) 論文集, pp.49-54 (2013.10) 加藤佑典，渡邊大輔，中條拓伯:&amp;ldquo;スケーラブル回路分割機構における信号情報格納・再生方式&amp;rdquo;,組込みシステムシンポジウム(ESS2013)論文集, pp.164-165 (2013.10) 渡邊大輔，加藤佑典，中條拓伯:&amp;ldquo;スケーラブル回路分割機構におけるハードウェア拡張プロトコルの実装&amp;rdquo;,組込みシステムシンポジウム(ESS2013)論文集, pp.166-167 (2013.10) 査読なし研究会報告 加藤佑典，渡邊大輔，中條拓伯：&amp;ldquo;スケーラブル・ハードウェア機構における信号情報格納・再生方式&amp;rdquo;，信学技報，CPSY2013-77，pp.25-30 (2014.01). 渡邊大輔，加藤佑典，中條拓伯：&amp;ldquo;スケーラブル・ハードウェア機構におけるハードウェア拡張プロトコル&amp;rdquo;，信学技報，CPSY2013-77，pp.31-36 (2014.01). 著書 John L. Hennessy (著), David A. Patterson (著),中條拓伯 (監修, 訳), 吉瀬謙二 (訳), 佐藤寿倫 (訳), 天野英晴 (監修, 訳), 鈴木貢 (訳)：&amp;ldquo;コンピュータアーキテクチャ 定量的アプローチ 第5版&amp;rdquo;，翔泳社，ISBN-13: 9784798126234 (2014.</description></item><item><title>2012年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2012/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2012/</guid><description>論文誌 小池恵介, 太田淳, 大島浩太, 藤波香織, 郡信幸, 竹本正志, 中條拓伯:&amp;ldquo;Android におけるJavaアプリケーションのFPGAアクセラレーション&amp;rdquo;,情報処理学会論文誌「組込みシステム」特集号 Vol.53, No.12, pp.2740-2751 ( 2012.12) 国際会議 Atsushi Ohta, Daisuke Yoshizane, Hironori Nakajo:&amp;ldquo;Cost Reduction in Migrating Execution Modes in a Dalvik Accelerator&amp;rdquo;,Proc. 1st IEEE Global Conf.Consumer Electronics (GCCE 2012), pp.502-506 (2012.10) Hironori Nakajo, Keisuke Koike and Kaori Fujinami: &amp;ldquo;FPGA Acceleration with a Reconfigurable Android for the Future Embedded Devices&amp;rdquo;, Proc. Int. Workshop on Performance, Applications, and Parallelism for Android and HTML5 (PAPAH), pp173-178 (2012.</description></item><item><title>2011年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2011/</guid><description>論文誌 Pulung Waskito, Shinobu Miwa, Yasue Mitsukura and Hironori Nakajo:&amp;ldquo;Evaluation of GPU-based Empirical Mode Decomposition for Off-line Analysis&amp;rdquo;,IEICE Transactions, Vol. E94-D, No.12, pp.2328-2337 (2011.12) 太田淳，三輪忍，中條拓伯:&amp;ldquo;Android端末におけるハードウェアによるJavaの高速化手法の提案&amp;rdquo;,情報処理学会論文誌コンピューティングシステム, Vol.4, No.3, pp.115-132 (2011.5) （2011年度コンピュータサイエンス領域奨励賞） 国際会議 Hironor Nakajo, Keisuke Koike, Atsushi Ohta, Kohta Ohshima, Kaori Fujinami:&amp;ldquo;Reconfigurable Android with an FPGA Accelerator for the Future Embedded Devices&amp;rdquo;,Proc. of the 3rd Workshop on Ultra Performance and Dependable Acceleration Systems (UPDAS2011), pp.173-178 (2011.12). Noboru Tanabe, Boonyasitpichai Nuttapon, Hironori Nakajo, Yuka Ogawa, Junko Kogou, Masami Takata and Kazuki Joe:&amp;ldquo;A Memory Accelerator with Gather Functions for Bandwidth-bound Irregular Applications&amp;rdquo;,Proc.</description></item><item><title>2010年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2010/</guid><description>論文誌 三輪 忍, 張 鵬, 横山 弘基, 堀部 悠平, 中條 拓伯: &amp;ldquo;キャッシュを用いたレジスタ・マップ表の回路面積削減&amp;rdquo;， 情報処理学会論文誌 コンピューティングシステム, Vol.3, No.3, pp.44-55 (2010.9). 国際会議 P. Waskito, S. Miwa, Y. Mitsukura and H. Nakajo: &amp;ldquo;Parallelizing Hilbert-Huang Transform on GPU&amp;rdquo;,The 2nd Workshop on Ultra Performance and Dependable Acceleration Systems (UPDAS'10), pp.184-190 (2010.11). H.Yokoyama, Y.Horibe, P.Zhang, S.Miwa, H.Nakajo: &amp;ldquo;An Effective Replacement Policy Focusing on Lifetime of a Cache Line&amp;rdquo;,Proceedings of the 2010 International Conference on Computer Design (CDES2010), pp.</description></item><item><title>2009年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2009/</guid><description>論文誌 N. Tanabe, H. Hakozaki, H. Ando, Y. Dohi, Z. Luo and H. Nakajo :&amp;ldquo;An enhancer of memory and network for applications with largecapacity data and non-continuous data accessing&amp;rdquo;, Journal of Supercomputing, Springer, Dec. 2009, doi : 10.1007/s11227-009-0373-7. (2010.3) 小笠原 嘉泰，三輪 忍，中條 拓伯:&amp;ldquo;SMTプロセッサにおけるL1/L2キャッシュアクセス動的切替方式&amp;rdquo;,情報処理学会論文誌 コンピューティングシステム (ACS), vol.2, No.3, pp.12-25, (2009.9) J. Yao, K. Ogata, H. Shimada, S. Miwa, H. Nakashima and S. Tomita:&amp;ldquo;An Instruction Scheduler for Dynamic ALU Cascading Adoption&amp;rdquo;,情報処理学会論文誌 コンピューティングシステム (ACS), vol.</description></item><item><title>2008年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2008/</guid><description>論文誌 国際会議 Noboru Tanabe and Hironori Nakajo:&amp;ldquo;High Performance Computing and Database Processing with COTS and Extended Memory Modules&amp;rdquo;,International Conference &amp;amp; Exhibition HPC Asia 2009, (2009.3). (Best Paper Award) N. Tanabe, H. Nakajo:&amp;ldquo;An Enhancer of Memory and Network for Cluster and Its Applications&amp;quot;International Conference on Parallel and Distributed Computing,Applications and Technologies (PDCAT'08), pp.99-106 (2008.12). N. Tanabe, H. Nakajo:&amp;ldquo;Introduction to Acceleration for MPI Derived Datatypes Using an Enhancer of Memory and Network&amp;rdquo;,The 15th European PVM/MPI Users&amp;rsquo; Group Conference (EuroPVM/MPI'08), pp.</description></item><item><title>2007年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2007/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2007/</guid><description>論文誌 小笠原嘉泰，佐藤未来子，並木美太郎，中條拓伯 :&amp;ldquo;SMTプロセッサにおけるキャッシュリプレース動的切替え方式&amp;quot;情報処理学会論文誌, Vol.48, No.SIG13(ACS19), pp.70-83 (2007.8). 宮部保雄，宮代具隆，北村聡，田邊昇，中條拓伯，天野英晴：&amp;ldquo;MPI派生データ型通信支援機構のDIMMnet-2への実装と評価&amp;quot;情報処理学会論文誌, Vol.48, No.SIG13(ACS19), pp.166-177 (2007 K.Sasada, M.Sato, S.Kawahara, N.Kato, M.Yamato, H.Nakajo, M.Namiki:&amp;ldquo;Efficient Implementation of Thread Library for Multithreaded Architecture&amp;rdquo;,The Journal of Future Generation Computer Systems (appear). 国際会議 Noboru Tanabe, Hironori Nakajo:Collaboration with a Small Accelerator on NIC and a Cache-based CPU for Scalable MPI Queue Processing,International Workshop on Innovative Architecture for Future Generation High-Performance Processors and Systems (IWIA'08), (2008.1). S.Watanabe, Y.Ogasawara, I.Tate, H.</description></item><item><title>2006年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2006/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2006/</guid><description>論文誌 佐藤 未来子, 笹田 耕一, 内倉 要, 小笠原 嘉泰, 品川 高廣, 中條 拓伯,並木 美太郎:&amp;ldquo;マルチスレッドアーキテクチャOChiMuS PE 向けシステムソフトウェアにおけるスレッド固有メモリの管理方式&amp;rdquo;電子情報通信学会論文誌D分冊, Vol.J90-D, No.3, pp.837-847 (2007.3). 小笠原 嘉泰, 佐藤 未来子, 笹田 耕一, 内倉 要, 並木 美太郎, 中條 拓伯：&amp;ldquo;SMTプロセッサ向けキャッシュメモリリプレース方式&amp;rdquo;,情報処理学会論文誌, Vol.47, No.SIG12(ACS15), pp.119-132 (2006.9) 北村 聡、宮部 保雄、中條 拓伯、田邊 昇、天野 英晴：&amp;ldquo;メッセージパッシングモデルを支援するパケット受信機構のDIMMnet-2への実装と評価&amp;rdquo;,情報処理学会論文誌コンピューティングシステム, Vol.47, No.SIG12(ACS15), pp 59-73 (2006.9) 査読付国際会議 Ippei Tate, Yoshiyasu Ogasawara, Mikiko Sato, Koichi Sasada, Kaname Uchikura, Kazunari Asano, Satoshi Watanabe, Mitaro Namiki and Hironori Nakajo:&amp;ldquo;Implementable Models of SMT Processor into FPGA&amp;rdquo;,The 2006 International Conference on Parallel and Distributed Processing Techniques and Applications (PDPTA'06), Vol.</description></item><item><title>2005年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2005/</guid><description>発表論文 内倉要, 佐藤未来子, 笹田耕一, 加藤義人, 大和仁典, 中條拓伯, 並木美太郎：&amp;ldquo;SMT プロセッサにおけるスレッドスケジューラの開発&amp;rdquo;, 情報処理学会論文誌, Vol.46, No.SIG12(ACS11), pp.150-160 (2005.8) 北村聡, 濱田芳博, 宮部保雄, 宮代具隆,伊沢徹, 田邊昇, 中條拓伯, 天野英晴:&amp;ldquo;DIMMnet-2 ネットワークインタフェースコントローラの設計と実装&amp;rdquo;,情報処理学会論文誌アドバンスドコンピューティングシステム, Vol.46, No.SIG12(ACS11), pp.13-26 (2005) 田邊昇，安藤宏, 箱崎博孝, 土肥康孝, 中條拓伯, 天野英晴:&amp;ldquo;プリフェッチ機能を有するメモリモジュールによるPC上での間接参照の高速化&amp;rdquo;,情報処理学会論文誌アドバンスドコンピューティングシステム, Vol.46, No.SIG12(ACS11), pp.1-12 (2005) 笹田耕一, 佐藤未来子, 内倉要, 小笠原嘉泰, 中條拓伯, 並木美太郎：&amp;ldquo;SMT プロセッサ向けの軽量な同期機構&amp;rdquo;, 情報処理学会論文誌, Vol.46, No.SIG16(ACS12), pp.14-27 (2005.12) 佐藤未来子, 笹田耕一, 内倉要, 小笠原嘉泰, 品川高廣, 中條拓伯, 並木美太郎:&amp;ldquo;マルチスレッドアーキテクチャにおけるスレッド固有メモリの管理方式&amp;rdquo;,情報処理学会コンピュータシステムシンポジウム2005論文集,Vol.2005, No.18, pp.99-108 (2005.11) 査読付国際会議 Noboru Tanabe, Akira Kitamura, Tomotaka Miyashiro, Yasuo Miyabe, Tohru Izawa, Yoshihiro Hamada, Hironori Nakajo and Hideharu Amano: &amp;ldquo;Preliminary Evaluations of a FPGA-based-Prototype of DIMMnet-2 Network Interface&amp;rdquo;, Proc.</description></item><item><title>2004年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2004/</guid><description>発表論文 佐藤未来子, 笹田耕一, 加藤義人, 大和仁典, 河原章二, 中條拓伯, 並木美太郎, &amp;ldquo;マルチスレッドアーキテクチャ向けOS「Future」におけるプロセス管理&amp;rdquo;, 情報処理学会論文誌, Vol.45, No.SIG3(ACS5), pp.38-49 (2004.3) K.Sasada, M.Sato, S.Kawahara, N.Kato, M.Yamato, H.Nakajo, M.Namiki: &amp;ldquo;Efficient Implementation of Thread Library for Multithreaded Architecture&amp;rdquo;, The Journal of Future Generation Computer Systems (appear) 査読付国際会議 Noboru Tanabe, Noboru Tanabe, Masasige Nakatake, Hiritaka Hakozaki, Yasunori Dohi, Hironori Nakajo and Hideharu Amano : &amp;ldquo;A New Memory Module for COTS-Based Personal Supercomputing&amp;rdquo;, Proc. of 7th Int. Workshop on Innovative Architecture for Future Generation High-Performance Processors and Systems (IWIA2004), pp.</description></item><item><title>2003年 論文・発表</title><link>/studies/2003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/studies/2003/</guid><description>発表論文 田邊昇，濱田芳博，山本淳二，今城英樹，中條拓伯，工藤知宏，天野英晴: &amp;ldquo;DIMMスロット搭載型ネットワークインタフェースDIMMnet-1とその低遅延通信機構AOTF&amp;rdquo;， 情報処理学会論文誌 ハイパフォーマンスコンピューティングシステム， Vol44, No.SIG1(HPS 6), pp.10-23(2003.01) 大音真由美，中條拓伯，城和貴: &amp;ldquo;Webコミュニティ検索のための量子アルゴリズムの提案と検証&amp;rdquo;, 情報処理学会論文誌 数理モデル化と応用， Vol.43, No.SIG7 (TOM8), pp.26-34 (2003.5) 笹田耕一, 佐藤未来子, 河原章二, 加藤義人, 大和仁典, 中條拓伯, 並木美太郎: &amp;ldquo;マルチスレッドアーキテクチャにおけるスレッドライブラリの実現と評価&amp;rdquo;, 情報処理学会論文誌, Vol.44, No.SIG11(ACS3), pp.215-225 (2003.9). 査読付国際会議 Noboru Tanabe, Yoshihiro Hamada, Akihiro Mitsuhashi, Hironori Nakajo, Junji Yamamoto, Hideki Imashiro, Tomohiro Kudoh, Hideharu Amano: &amp;ldquo;Performance Evaluation of Bandwidth and Global Operations on DIMMnet-1 Prototype&amp;rdquo;, Proc. of 6th Int. Workshop on Innovative Architecture for Future Generation High-Performance Processors and Systems (IWIA2003) pp.</description></item></channel></rss>